It's summer, all right.
You should wear this. It's quite hot today.
Thanks, Shikimori-san.
Come on, Izumi-san, let's hurry!
Sure!
We worked hard on those exams!
Now it's time to play hard!
Hey, we're on break!
Why'd you have to bring up exams?!
Don't dredge up that memory.
Hey, that's all on you.
Consecutive Failing Grades
Be glad you only have to
take supplementary lessons.
Hey, guys! We're here.
We're gonna play our hearts out today!
Yeah!
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#05  Jolly Times at the River!
Oh, there it is!
The river!
It's a miracle the weather's
this nice when Izumi's with us!
That was low-key brutal.
Right, Izumi?!
It's true!
I'm so glad I made all those
teru teru bouzu dolls!
Usually Brings Rain
Are you in grade school?
Anyway...
Let's start the barbecue!
I haven't eaten anything all day.
You're drooling.
They're wild beasts...
Chow time!
I'll leave the vegetables here.
Okay.
I held out until this meat was
on sale at the grocery store!
Hey, that looks tasty.
More praise, please!
We borrowed everything we'd need
and we have all our food, so...
Why don't we divide up the prep work?
Heck, yeah!
Why'd you volunteer yourself to cut
vegetables with those knife skills?!
I thought I could do it if I tried...
So says the defendant.
Knock that off!
We'll handle this! You just sit down!
Let me help, then.
That's an even worse idea!
Are we in Hell?
Izumi! Don't do anything rash!
Please, God...
Izumi, you can cook?
Yeah.
I help my mom a lot, so I can
probably make just about anything.
Huh?!
I-I had no idea...
Wait, Izumi, if you can cook that well,
shouldn't girls be falling all over you?
Please don't say weird things like that.
Are you after him?
Why are you getting all
competitive toward me?
Let's put some more on!
Good idea!
That sound is making my mouth water!
Think they're ready?
Not yet. Be patient.
Done!
Izumi-san, please have this if you'd like.
Ajillo?
I made it just for you.
Oh, wow! It looks great!
No fair, Izumi!
It smells so good.
Irresistible.
Shikimori-san really can do anything.
I-Is there something wrong with it?
Oh, no! It just looks so good,
I was at a loss for words.
I'm really happy.
I'll try it now.
I mean, she's cute, she's smart,
she's athletic, and she can cook?
Shikimori-san is perfect in every single...
Izumi-san?!
Huh?
Wh-What is this? It burns!
And it's bitter. No... Sweet?!
It's so intense that I thought my tongue
was exploding right out of my mouth!
H-Huh? Does it really taste that...
I guess she's not so good
at cooking after all.
I've got tissues.
Need some water?
There's juice, too.
Izumi-san?
Please spit that out! It could be deadly!
It's okay.
You put your all into making this for me.
I get seasonings wrong all the time, too.
Please, body... hold out!
I swear...
I'll learn how to make delicious meals.
Just you wait.
Okay. I'll look forward to it.
Well played.
Impressive.
Whew, I'm stuffed.
He's still glutting himself.
Growth spurts are scary.
Hmm... Anyone else feel like something sweet?
Did we bring any dessert?
Yes.
I made s'mores from the snacks we brought.
S'mores?
You toast a marshmallow and sandwich it
between crackers and chocolate.
Who came up with this work of art?!
Thank you, God.
Wow...
Actually...
I really wanted you to try these.
I-I'll try one right now!
You ate too many.
What do you think?
It's delicious.
Really?
Really.
I could eat these every day.
G-G... Glad to hear it!
"Every day," she says.
Shameless!
Sh-She didn't mean it like that!
Right, Shikimori-san?!
Who knows?
Stop teasing me!
She's a devil...
Man, I'm stuffed!
Okay, everything's cleaned up.
Thanks!
All right, let's hit that river!
Yeah!
About before...
Hmm?
Next time, let's have them
with just the two of us.
Yeah.
Ooh, that's cold!
It's nice, isn't it?
Y-Yes, it is.
Huh? Is something wrong, Shikimori-san?
N-No! I was just thinking
about how relaxing the river is.
Here I am.
Oh, wow!
A giant shell!
The kids are loving it!
Where were you even keeping that?!
Just swim like a normal person.
I guess I'll leave it to the kids.
Don't put it in the water.
Okay!
Wow, I guess some modern swimsuits are
made to look like Western clothes.
That's cool.
Y-Yes, I guess so!
Come on in, you two.
I-Izumi-san, let's go join them.
Sure.
All that aside, the river's so nice and cool.
I should thank everyone.
Even the kids here are having fun.
The current's taking her?!
Micchon!
So when's the big reveal?
W-Well, I, uh...
You bought it just for your bae, didn't you?
I... I don't think... I can do it.
Hey, where's Izumi?
Mommy...
Hi there—
Ow, ow, ow! D-Don't get violent!
Let's go back to your mom, okay?
See? Nothing to be scared of anymore.
I'm not a great swimmer,
but I have to get her back to safety.
Can you reach?
Uh-huh.
Thank goodness.
Ooh!
Mister?!
Izumi-san!
Izumi!
Mister!
Are you okay?
That guy... He's...
Wh-What do we do?!
Should we call someone?!
My foot cramped up...
Wait, this is really bad...
I... can't breathe...
It's okay.
Everything's okay now.
Thanks, Shikimori-san.
Ow!
Why didn't you call for me?
S-Sorry...
You guys! Are you okay?!
Oh, thank God you're both okay!
Don't underestimate the river! It'll kill you!
If you're hurt, say so.
Okay. Thanks.
Thank you so much!
I'm so sorry this happened!
M-Ma'am?!
Thank you.
And I'm sorry. Did I scare you?
Nuh-uh.
You were really cool!
Wha—
Thank you... You're so kind...
All right! Back to the fun!
Hey, cheer up! She's just a little kid.
Maybe I'll swim, too.
Are you insane?!
He bounces back quick.
Yahoo!
Whee!
Take that!
Now you've done it!
That's cold!
Take that!
Neko, there's a fish.
What? Where?
Yah!
Hey, where'd it go?
Shikimori-san...
Your swimsuit is really cute.
Just now?!
Konjac
Souvenirs
Miso Pickles
Miso-Preserved Pork
Boy Choy
Manjuu
This is it.
How do I look?
Really cute.
Baron of Local Specialties
That suits you so well!
Thanks for picking it out
for me, Hachimitsu-san.
Stop. You'll make me blush.
What's going on there?
GELATO
Made with milk from local dairy farmers
20 Flavors of Gelato
It's an ice cream shop.
Oh, they've got gelato!
Looks pretty popular.
Ice cream!
Let's go get some.
Where's everyone?
They're still waiting in line.
It is pretty busy.
We had to wait quite a while.
Yum!
Yours looks good, too. What flavor is it?
I think it was... mocha almond, if I recall.
Wow...
Do you want a taste?
Can I? I'd love to!
Thanks!
What's the matter?
Oh, uh... I just...
Nothing.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Then I'll try yours, too.
Nom!
My... My ice cream...
No, that was mine!
Sorry, man! Here, you can have mine.
Jeez...
Hey! What are you, a little kid?!
Throb
Serves you right.
You took damage from that, though!
Gimme! Gimme! Gimme!
Who's the little kid?!
My ice cream!
Guys, we're in high school...
How dare you eat Izumi-san's?!
Is ice cream worth all this?
Grudges over food are scary.
Ice cream is truly sinful.
Mm, this is the best!
Time flies, huh? How is it so late already?
Man, I played like crazy today.
Ready to head home?
No! Not yet!
The real world awaits!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
The place is all ours! Let's grab seats!
It sure is hot.
Wanna open a window?
The sweetfish was delicious, wasn't it?
Look. This was you eating sweetfish, Inu.
Don't drop the "zuka."
The line for the ice cream sure was crazy.
Sure was.
Wait, is Hachimitsu asleep?
Is she breathing?
She's dead.
Oh, crap. I just dozed off for a second.
Mph... Me, too.
All three of them are asleep.
Yes... they are...
Wow, she's spent.
You can sleep, Shikimori-san.
What'd you say?
She's so cute!
G-Gotta think about something else...
Um... Um...
Today sure was fun!
I caused everyone a lot of stress,
but it was nice to play
to our hearts' content.
Going shopping was fun, too.
And the cucumbers were great.
I hope Mom and Dad like the
souvenirs I got for them.
This really was fun.
And I guess that's because
I was with these guys.
I'm glad I got to be friends them...
and that I met Shikimori-san.
I'm really... so glad...
Huh?
Can't walk any more...
The indoorsy types are dead!
SEE YOU~